hamweather.net 2017-09-11

# AerisWeather

Last Updated:  December 15, 2016

This policy explains our information practices, defines your privacy options and describes how your information is collected and used.  

This policy covers this website (the “AW Website”) and the various web, desktop and mobile applications (collectively the “Applications”) made available by Whether or Knot LLC, d/b/a AerisWeather (“AW”).  The AW Website and the Applications are owned and operated by AW, a company organized under the laws of Minnesota.  Should you have privacy questions or concerns, send an email to [privacy@aerisweather.com](mailto:privacy@aerisweather.com).

By using or visiting the AW Website or using the Applications, you agree to the collection and use of information in the manner described in this policy. AW shall have right at any time and without prior notice, at its sole discretion, to revise this policy.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email, by means of a notice the next time you log in to the AW Website, by means of a notice on the AW Website homepage or when you next activate the Application. Such revisions and additions shall be effective immediately upon notice. You are responsible for reviewing the AW Website or Applications periodically for any modification to this policy.  Any access or use of the AW Website or Applications by you after notice of modifications to this policy shall constitute and be deemed to be your agreement to such modifications.

### THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

This policy applies to all information collected on the AW Website, any information you provide to AW and any information that results from your use of Applications. You will most likely provide us personal information to us when you register as a user of AW Website, license and then use the Applications or participate in certain AW promotions or events. The personal information we may collect might include: passwords, user names, addresses, email addresses, phone numbers and credit/debit card numbers and PayPal and ACH account information and instructions.

### THE APPLICATIONS

Use of the Applications is subject to the terms and conditions of the Application License Agreement ([www.aerisweather.com/support/docs/license](https://www.aerisweather.com/support/docs/license)).

### BLOGS AND PRODUCT REVIEWS

The AW Website or Applications may include blogs, product reviews or other message areas that allow users to post or send information to the AW Website or the Applications. When you post information to the AW Website or Applications, others can also view that information.  We urge you to exercise caution when providing personally identifiable information to AW, AW Website or the Applications.

### OUR COLLECTION OF YOUR DATA

In addition to the personal information you supply, we may collect certain information to (1) evaluate how visitors, guests, and customers use the AW Website or the Applications; or (2) provide you with personalized information or offers.  We collect data to make the AW Website and Applications work better for you in the following ways: to improve the design of the AW Website and Applications, to provide personalization on the AW Website and Applications and to evaluate the performance of our marketing programs. The technologies we may use to gather this non-personal information may include “IP” addresses, “cookies”, browser detection, “weblogs” and various “geo-location” tools.

### HOW WE COLLECT AND USE INFORMATION

Our primary goal in collecting your information is to provide you with a personalized, relevant, and positive experience with the AW Website and Applications.

You can register on the AW Website or the Applications to receive promotions and updates, or to be contacted for market research purposes. You can control your privacy preferences regarding such marketing communications (see the section below entitled “Your Privacy Preferences”).

From time to time, you may be invited to participate in optional customer surveys or promotions, and AW may request that you provide some or all of the above listed personal information in those surveys or promotions. We use information collected from surveys and promotions to learn about our customers in order to improve our services and develop new products and services of interest to our customers.

IP addresses define the Internet location of computers and help us better understand the geographic distribution of our visitors and customers and manage the performance of the AW Website. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer when you visit the AW Website, so we can immediately recognize you when you return to the AW Website and deliver content specific to your interests. You may modify your browser preferences to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is set, or reject all cookies. Please consult your browser instructions for information on how to modify your choices about cookies.  If you modify your browser preferences, certain features of the AW Website may not be available to you.

We may detect the type of web browser you are using to optimize the performance of the AW Website and to understand the mix of browsers used by our visitors, guests, and customers. To learn about how people use our site, we examine weblogs, which show the paths people take through the AW Website and how long they spend in certain areas.

The Applications may include the ability to link certain geographical information made available by us with your physical location. When you use the Applications, the Applications may know, in very general terms, your current physical location.  To the extent that your physical location can be determined by the Applications, we may use your location to make available information to you that is relevant because of your physical location.

We may also compile certain general information related to your use of the Website and Applications.  You agree that we are authorized to use, reproduce and generally make such information available to third parties in the aggregate, provided that your information shall not include personally identifiable information about you or be attributable to you.

AW may contract with unaffiliated third parties to provide services such as website or application hosting, advertising, customer communications, data analytics and other services. When we do this, we may provide your personally identifiable information to third parties only to provide those services, and they are not authorized to use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

### OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

Access to your personal data is limited to authorized AW staff or approved vendors. Although total security does not exist on the Internet or through mobile networks, AW shall make commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the information that you submit to AW.  

### USE OF THE AW WEBSITE AND APPLICATIONS BY CHILDREN

**THE AW WEBSITE AND THE APPLICATIONS ARE NOT INTENDED FOR USE BY CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13.**

### YOUR PRIVACY PREFERENCES

When you sign up as a registered user of the AW Website or Applications you may begin receiving marketing communications such as e-mail newsletters, product and service updates and promotions. Our customers generally find this type of information useful. If you do not want to receive these updates, you must “opt-out” by unchecking the “Add me to the mailing list” box on the registration page, or should you choose to opt-out after registering, you can select the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email and follow the opt-out instructions.

### HOW TO ACCESS OR CORRECT YOUR INFORMATION

Send AW an email at [privacy@aerisweather.com](mailto:privacy@aerisweather.com) if you want to access, review or correct your personally identifiable information collected by AW. To protect your privacy and security, AW requires a user ID and password to verify your identity before granting you the right to access, review or make corrections to your personally identifiable information.

### DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process.  It is also possible that AW would sell its business (by merger, acquisition or otherwise) or sell all or substantially all of its assets.  In any transaction of this kind, customer information, including your personally identifiable information, may be among the assets that are transferred. If we decide to so transfer your personally identifiable information, you will be notified by an email sent to the last known email address in our files, by notice posted on the AW Website or when you activate the Applications.

### PRIVACY AND OTHER WEBSITES AND APPLICATIONS

The AW Website or the Applications may contain links to other websites or other mobile applications. AW is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites or applications. This policy only applies to information collected by AW.
